[
  {
    "number": "1",
    "question": "What has been the highest combat level in runescape to date?",
    "correctAnswer": "200",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "152",
      "138",
      "170"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "2",
    "question": "After the initial release in 2001, what was the first skill added?",
    "correctAnswer": "Crafting",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fishing",
      "Fletching",
      "Thieving"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "3",
    "question": "Which quest replaced Romeo & Juliet?",
    "correctAnswer": "Gunnar's Ground",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Death of Chivalry",
      "Heartstealer",
      "What's mine is yours"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "4",
    "question": "What item is atop the Lumbridge gatehouse?",
    "correctAnswer": "Bronze pickaxe",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bronze hatchet",
      "Bronze longsword",
      "Bronze battleaxe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "5",
    "question": "From where would you have been able to receive the commander title?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mobilising Armies",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soul Wars",
      "Fist of Guthix",
      "Clan Wars"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "6",
    "question": "How many shards create an item?",
    "correctAnswer": "120",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "100",
      "60",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "7",
    "question": "Which river separates Morytania from the Kingdom of Misthalin?",
    "correctAnswer": "River Salve",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "River Lum",
      "River Dougne",
      "River Elid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "8",
    "question": "What's the overload formula?",
    "correctAnswer": "15% of level + 3",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "10% of level +5",
      "12% of level +3",
      "15% of level +2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "9",
    "question": "What drops instead of an HSR without and LOTD?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cheese + Tom Batta",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blurberry Special",
      "Worm Crunchies",
      "Chocolate Bomb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "10",
    "question": "How many beacons can be lit in the minigame, All Fired Up?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "13",
      "12",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "11",
    "question": "What is Barakur?",
    "correctAnswer": "Dwarf",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Elf",
      "Human",
      "Goblin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "12",
    "question": "What was the first skill to reach level 120?",
    "correctAnswer": "Dungeoneering",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Archaeology",
      "Invention",
      "Slayer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "13",
    "question": "What combat level is the King Black Dragon?",
    "correctAnswer": "276",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "275",
      "273",
      "282"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "14",
    "question": "Who owned the Ring of Charos before the player?",
    "correctAnswer": "Dr Fenkenstrain",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charos",
      "Vanstrom Klause",
      "Roavar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "15",
    "question": "What city was Jagex founded?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cambridge",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oxford",
      "London",
      "Bristol"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "16",
    "question": "Which has the highest possible life points?",
    "correctAnswer": "Vorkath",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Zamorak, Lord of Chaos",
      "Seiryu the Azure Serpent",
      "Solak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "17",
    "question": "What is the highest enrage at Telos",
    "correctAnswer": "4000",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1000",
      "2000",
      "60000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "18",
    "question": "What is the newest combat style in Runescape?",
    "correctAnswer": "Necromancy",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Magic",
      "Ranged",
      "Strength"
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": "19",
    "question": "What is the lowest combat level to wear Void Knights equipment?",
    "correctAnswer": "51",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "48",
      "55",
      "42"
    ]
  }
]